Coming up on Small Doses Podcast.
Hey, what's up, y'all? I am your girl, Candy.
Hey, it's Don't Call Me White Girl.
Hello, my name is Christina Brown.
Hey, what's up? I'm Eleni Fiona.
Hey, y'all, this is Shirley, a.k.a. Beauty to the Streets,
and I'm doing Small Doses Podcast.
And today we're talking about the side effects of girl group dynamics,
side effects of diaspora wars, the side effects of integrity.
Side effects of being light-skinned with my girl, Amanda Seals.
Shout out to the Seals Squad.
You can not only listen, now you can watch.
Every Thursday we are premiering 4 p.m. Pacific, 7 p.m. Eastern
at YouTube, Amanda Seals TV, and I will be there in the chat with y'all.
I will see you there.